{
    "id": "3c11d3ec262f465694a20eaa3cff1f08",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "No sooner did the plane land ……………………. there was a loud explosion.",
            "description": "No sooner is a comparative expression use than after it. ",
            "answers": [
                "then",
                "than",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The germ is ……………………….. small to be seen with the eye.",
            "description": "Note the pattern too..to..",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must take the tablets ………………………….. get well.",
            "description": "To and in order to show purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in order to",
                "in order that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ did the hunter raise his gun than the birds flew away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "Hardly",
                "No sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I had no ticket, I was able to get in.",
            "description": "Although is similar to but in meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Even if",
                "Even so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t talk …………………………. they are singing.",
            "description": "While can be used to talk about two simultaneous events. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "while",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "People live ………………………… the climate is good.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "which",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is too intelligent ……………………. be fooled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so as to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. my exams are over, I am free.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Now that",
                "That",
                "The fact that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… she was sleeping, I left without meeting her.",
            "description": "Since shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "Though",
                "Hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. carefully you drive, accidents can still happen.",
            "description": "However means it doesn't matter how.",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "How",
                "How ever"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The hall is  ……………………….. to accommodate all guests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough spacious",
                "spacious enough",
                "too spacious"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}